{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20result%20of%2018%20minus%20%2812%20divided%20by%204%29%3F",
      "correct_answer": "15",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "9",
        "12",
        "18"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20value%20of%201.5%20times%20%2810%20plus%203%29%3F",
      "correct_answer": "19.5",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "21",
        "18",
        "20"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20square%20root%20of%20144%20minus%208%3F",
      "correct_answer": "4",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2",
        "6",
        "8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20%283%20times%204%29%20plus%20%282%20times%205%29%3F",
      "correct_answer": "22",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "20",
        "24",
        "18"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20%2810%20percent%20of%2020%29%20plus%20%2820%20percent%20of%2010%29%3F",
      "correct_answer": "4",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "6",
        "8",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20average%20of%2030%2C%2040%2C%20and%2050%3F",
      "correct_answer": "40",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "35",
        "45",
        "50"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20%282%20to%20the%20power%20of%203%29%20times%20%2810%20divided%20by%202%29%3F",
      "correct_answer": "40",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "30",
        "50",
        "20"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20%2820%20percent%20of%2025%29%20minus%203%3F",
      "correct_answer": "2",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "3",
        "1",
        "4"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20result%20of%20%28100%20divided%20by%205%29%20plus%20%285%20times%202%29%3F",
      "correct_answer": "30",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "20",
        "15",
        "25"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20%285%20squared%29%20minus%20%2810%20times%204%29%20plus%203%3F",
      "correct_answer": "-12",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2",
        "-10",
        "-5"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
